{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Do you have any severe allergies? ",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Yes"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "No"
                }
            ],
            "score":4,
            "correctAnswer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "What’s your kid’s favourite food dish?  ",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Burger"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Burrito"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "Chips"
                }
            ],
            "score":4,
            "correctAnswer": "Burrito"
        },
        {
            "question": "What’s your spouse’s favourite color ? ",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Blue"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Red"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "Green"
                }
            ],
            "score":4,
            "correctAnswer": "Blue"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you have any investment plans for your kids/spouse?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Yes"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "No"
                }
            ],
            "score":3,
            "correctAnswer": "Yes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which was the last family gathering you attended? ",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Tim's retirement party"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Anniversary celebration of Kristin and Julien "
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "Nick’s birthday party "
                }
            ],
            "score":3,
            "correctAnswer": "Tim's retirement party"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which university you graduated from?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "University of Leicester"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "University of Essex"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "University of London"
                }
            ],
            "score":3,
            "correctAnswer": "University of London"
        },
        {
            "question": "Hey what is your favourite dish ? ",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Shepherd's Pie"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Beef Wellington"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "Fish and Chips"
                }
            ],
            "score":2,
            "correctAnswer": "Shepherd's Pie"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which television show you like watching the most ?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "The Big Bang Theory"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "F.R.I.E.N.D.S."
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "The Suits "
                }
            ],
            "score":2,
            "correctAnswer": "F.R.I.E.N.D.S."
        },
        {
            "question": "What was your profession, was it business or a job ?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Job"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Business"
                }
            ],
            "score":2,
            "correctAnswer": "Job"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you like to spend your leisure time (hobby)?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Gardening"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Reading books"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "Squash"
                }
            ],
            "score":2,
            "correctAnswer": "Gardening"
        },
        {
            "question": "Out of all the places you have travelled so far, which is your most loved one?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Scotland"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Paris"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "San Fransico"
                }
            ],
            "score":2,
            "correctAnswer": "Paris"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where do you keep your car keys usually?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Wadrobe"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Garden"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "Drawer"
                }
            ],
            "score":2,
            "correctAnswer": "Drawer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you remember which was the brand of your very first car you owned?",
            "options": [
                {
                    "label": "A.",
                    "value": "Volkswagen"
                },
                {
                    "label": "B.",
                    "value": "Audi"
                },
                {
                    "label": "C.",
                    "value": "Tesla"
                }
            ],
            "score":2,
            "correctAnswer": "Volkswagen"
        }

 
    ]
}

